=Who Stole My Kiss=
= من سرق قبلتي =
=Episode 19=
= الحلقة 19 =
Miss Kelly.
ملكة جمال كيلي.
Did you see the news?
هل رأيت الأخبار؟
Let me explain.
دعني أوضح.
I was just about to look for you.
كنت على وشك البحث عنك.
Let's talk in the meeting room.
لنتحدث في غرفة الاجتماعات.
This matter went like that.
سارت هذه المسألة على هذا النحو.
My friend was trying to protect me the other day.
كان صديقي يحاول حمايتي في ذلك اليوم.
He definitely wasn't thinking of causing trouble.
بالتأكيد لم يكن يفكر في التسبب في المتاعب.
Mr. Chen, please trust me.
السيد تشين ، الرجاء ثق بي.
What the netizens wrote was fake.
ما كتبه مستخدمو الإنترنت كان مزيفًا.
Qin Mochi and I have nothing to do with each other.
تشين موتشي وأنا لا علاقة لنا ببعضنا البعض.
When I met Qin Mochi by chance
عندما قابلت تشين موتشي بالصدفة
at the cinema the other day,
في السينما ذلك اليوم ،
Miss Kelly was there as well.
كانت الآنسة كيلي هناك أيضًا.
Kelly, what happened?
كيلي ماذا حدث؟
We only met by chance the other day.
التقينا بالصدفة فقط في ذلك اليوم.
I left after greeting them.
غادرت بعد التحية عليهم.
I'm not sure
لست واثق
what happened after that.
ماذا حدث بعد ذلك.
Han Tingting, as a staff of the company,
هان تينجتينج ، بصفته أحد موظفي الشركة ،
you've never earned a dime for the company
لم تكسب قط سنتًا للشركة
and the company has been affected twice.
وتأثرت الشركة مرتين.
Mr. Chen,
السيد شين،
I was there the other day.
كنت هناك في ذلك اليوم.
I can testify that
أستطيع أن أشهد على ذلك
Han Tingting is telling the truth.
هان تينجتينج يقول الحقيقة.
It doesn't matter anymore.
لا يهم بعد الآن.
The most important thing is to stop the company's losses.
أهم شيء إيقاف خسائر الشركة.
We've decided to use
لقد قررنا استخدام
Qin Mochi as the ambassador of our new game.
تشين موتشي كسفير لعبتنا الجديدة.
So, the setting of the storyline
لذا ، فإن وضع القصة
and the character development
وتنمية الشخصية
must be amended.
يجب تعديله.
Qin Mochi has become the ambassador?
أصبح تشين موتشي السفير؟
Given the situation,
بالنظر إلى الوضع ،
we have to let him be the ambassador.
علينا أن نسمح له أن يكون السفير.
Miss Kelly,
ملكة جمال كيلي ،
did you and Qin Mochi...
هل أنت و تشين موتشي ...
Mr. Chen, I have yet
السيد تشين ، لدي حتى الآن
to tell Han Tingting about this.
لإخبار هان تينجتينج عن هذا الأمر.
She might need some time to get used to it.
قد تحتاج إلى بعض الوقت لتعتاد على ذلك.
Sure, execute it immediately.
بالتأكيد ، قم بتنفيذه على الفور.
I hope your collaboration
آمل تعاونك
will make a trending game
سوف تجعل اللعبة رائجة
and earn some money for the company.
وكسب بعض المال للشركة.
Mr. Chen, see you.
السيد تشين ، إلى اللقاء.
Miss Kelly.
ملكة جمال كيلي.
If we work with people like Qin Mochi,
إذا عملنا مع أشخاص مثل تشين موتشي ،
the company's benefits will be compromised.
سيتم المساس بمزايا الشركة.
It doesn't do you any good either.
إنه لا يفيدك أيضًا.
Han Tingting, you have two options.
هان تينجتينج ، لديك خياران.
Either
إما
you change the character and the storyline
قمت بتغيير الشخصية والقصة
based on Qin Mochi
على أساس تشين موتشي
or just resign.
أو مجرد الاستقالة.
We'll get another planner.
سنحصل على مخطط آخر.
Our team has changed the content many times.
قام فريقنا بتغيير المحتوى عدة مرات.
Why should we change it again?
لماذا يجب علينا تغييره مرة أخرى؟
Kelly, the project is now in the Alpha testing.
كيلي ، المشروع الآن في اختبار ألفا.
If we get someone to replace Tingting,
إذا حصلنا على شخص ما ليحل محل Tingting ،
it will affect the overall progress.
سيؤثر على التقدم العام.
It was because of her that
كان بسبب ذلك
our newly launched game
لعبتنا التي تم إطلاقها حديثًا
was boycotted by the netizens.
قاطعه مستخدمو الإنترنت.
Now, we're collaborating with Qin Mochi's company
الآن ، نحن نتعاون مع شركة Qin Mochi
to amend the mistake that she made.
لتعديل الخطأ الذي ارتكبته.
No matter what, this is our team's project.
بغض النظر عن ذلك ، هذا هو مشروع فريقنا.
Tingting's the main planner.
تينجتينج هو المخطط الرئيسي.
You shouldn't even interfere.
لا يجب أن تتدخلوا.
I'll talk to Mr. Chen.
سأتحدث مع السيد تشين.
Mr. Lu.
السيد.  شمس.
You let go of the chance to get promoted
لقد تركت فرصة الحصول على ترقية
because of her last time.
بسبب آخر مرة لها.
What?
لما؟
Are you going to tender resignation together with her?
هل ستقدمين استقالة معها؟
Do I need to explain to you
هل أحتاج أن أشرح لك
what I'm doing?
ماذا أفعل؟
You gave up on the promotion because of me?
هل تخليت عن الترقية بسببي؟
Do you think Mr. Chen
هل تعتقد أن السيد تشين
will listen to you?
سوف يستمع اليك
That's my business.
هذا عملي.
I know this matter happened because of you.
أعلم أن هذا الأمر حدث بسببك.
I don't care what's your relationship
لا يهمني ما علاقتك
with Qin Mochi.
مع تشين موتشي.
You need evidence to prove that.
أنت بحاجة إلى دليل لإثبات ذلك.
Enough!
كافٍ!
I'll resign.
سأستقيل.
(I'm not afraid of anything,)
(أنا لست خائفا من أي شيء،)
(but I'll not trouble others.)
(لكنني لن أزعج الآخرين.)
Tingting, don't worry.
تينجتينج ، لا تقلق.
I'll help you clarify this matter.
سأساعدك في توضيح هذا الأمر.
You've helped me a lot,
لقد ساعدتني كثيرا
but I can't get you in trouble anymore.
لكن لا يمكنني أن أوقعك في المشاكل بعد الآن.
You're my team member.
أنت عضو فريقي.
I need to be responsible for you.
أحتاج أن أكون مسؤولاً عنك.
Yesterday, my project has carried out the Alpha testing.
بالأمس ، أجرى مشروعي اختبار ألفا.
Today, something happened and I had to resign.
اليوم ، حدث شيء واضطررت إلى الاستقالة.
Maybe life
ربما الحياة
just likes to pull my legs.
فقط يحب سحب ساقي.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
what happened during our meal?
ماذا حدث خلال وجبتنا؟
I helped you to drink all the wine.
لقد ساعدتك على شرب كل النبيذ.
After that, you got drunk.
بعد ذلك ، سُكرت.
Do you remember what happened
هل تتذكر ما حدث
before I got you in the car?
قبل أن أركب السيارة؟
Tingting.
تينجتينج.
It's okay, master.
لا بأس يا معلمة.
He Rang, you're here.
هو رانغ ، أنت هنا.
Let me do it.
دعني افعلها.
Mr. Lu, thank you for taking care of me.
السيد لو ، شكرا لك على الاعتناء بي.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Let me tell you, Tingting.
دعني أخبرك يا تينجتينج.
I've cooked a lot of seafood for you.
لقد قمت بطهي الكثير من المأكولات البحرية من أجلك.
Congratulations
تهانينا
on escaping the trouble.
على الهروب من المتاعب.
Hold this for me.
امسك هذا من اجلي.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Something happened at home.
شيء ما حدث في المنزل.
There are reporters here.
هناك صحفيون هنا.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
We're the reporters from Dongcheng Entertainment.
نحن المراسلين من Dongcheng Entertainment.
Now, we've come to Han Tingting's house.
الآن ، جئنا إلى منزل هان تينجتينج.
Anybody home?
هل من احد بالمنزل؟
(Haiyuting)
(هاييوتينج)
Is Han Tingting home?
هل هان تينجتينج في المنزل؟
We're reporters.
نحن صحفيون.
Can you come out for an interview?
هل يمكنك الخروج لمقابلة؟
Look.
ينظر.
They're at the doorstep.
إنهم على عتبة الباب.
Why is this happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
I can't even go home now.
لا أستطيع حتى العودة إلى المنزل الآن.
The project was carrying out Alpha testing yesterday
كان المشروع يجري اختبار ألفا أمس
and we're asked to change the storyline today.
ونحن مطالبون بتغيير مسار القصة اليوم.
Also, she's being so firmed.
أيضا ، إنها متماسكة للغاية.
Something is not right.
شيء ما ليس صحيحا.
Maybe they're hooking up.
ربما هم يربطون.
Are you saying that
هل انت تقول هذا
Qin Mochi and Kelly are hooking up?
تشين موتشي وكيلي يتعاونان؟
You saw them at the cinema the other day.
رأيتهم في السينما ذلك اليوم.
Kelly must be thinking that you're a time bomb.
لابد أن كيلي يفكر في أنك قنبلة موقوتة.
She'll force you to resign one day.
ستجبرك على الاستقالة ذات يوم.
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
Look at what's happening.
انظر إلى ما يحدث.
I'm considered lucky if I'm not banned from the industry.
أنا أعتبر محظوظا إذا لم أكن ممنوعا من الصناعة.
I can't use my real name anymore
لا يمكنني استخدام اسمي الحقيقي بعد الآن
when I look for a new job.
عندما أبحث عن وظيفة جديدة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Although the Internet has memory,
على الرغم من أن الإنترنت به ذاكرة ،
it won't last long.
لن تدوم طويلا.
After a while,
بعد قليل،
no one will remember.
لن يتذكر أحد.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
If you can't find a job,
إذا لم تتمكن من العثور على وظيفة ،
just lie down at home.
فقط استلقِ في المنزل.
I'm able to feed you.
أنا قادر على إطعامك.
It's late now.
فوات الآن.
I'm tired.
انا تعب.
This place is too small.
هذا المكان صغير جدا.
I'll stay at my friend's place for a few days.
سأبقى في منزل صديقي لبضعة أيام.
I'm leaving. Bye.
سأرحل.  الوداع.
Wait, Xiaoxiao.
انتظر ، Xiaoxiao.
It's still bright out there.
لا يزال مشرقًا هناك.
(Oh no, it's just the two of us again.)
(أوه لا ، نحن اثنان فقط مرة أخرى.)
So many things have happened today.
لقد حدثت أشياء كثيرة اليوم.
You must be tired.
يجب أن تكون متعبا.
I'm indeed tired.
أنا متعب بالفعل.
Although it's not that late,
على الرغم من أن الوقت ليس متأخرًا ،
you know,
أنت تعرف،
I'm indeed tired.
أنا متعب بالفعل.
Why not you go back first?
لماذا لا تعود أولا؟
♪Does he like you?♪
♪ هل يحبك؟ ♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪ لا تتسرع في المقاطعة ♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪ أنت صامت ♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪ فقدت الشجاعة للحديث ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب ♪
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪ مطلوب
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪ احتضان أنفاسك ♪
♪Only you can♪
♪ أنت فقط تستطيع ♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪ حل اللغز اللطيف ♪
♪I like your♪
♪ أنا معجب بك ♪
♪Silly face♪
♪ وجه سخيف ♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪ فدائما ما تذكر السعادة
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪ إنها في أعماق قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب ♪
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
أمسكني بين ذراعيك ♪
♪I like♪
♪ أحب ♪
♪Being with you♪
التواجد معك ♪